<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Life on Corner case</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/tags/life/</link><description>Recent content in Life on Corner case</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Haisheng Wu</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2008 10:24:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://freizl.github.io/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Olympics 2008, Welcome to Beijing</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/olympics-2008-welcome-to-beijing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2008 10:24:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/olympics-2008-welcome-to-beijing/</guid><description>北京欢迎你
词：林夕 曲：小柯
迎接另一个晨曦，带来全新空气
气息改变情味不变，茶香飘满情谊
我家大门常打开，开放怀抱等你
拥抱过就有了默契，你会爱上这里
不管远近都是客人请不用客气
相约好了在一起，我们欢迎你
我家种着万年青，开放每段传奇
为传统的土壤播种，为你留下回忆
陌生熟悉都是客人请不用拘礼
第几次来没关系，有太多话题
北京欢迎你，为你开天辟地
流动中的魅力充满着朝气
北京欢迎你，在太阳下分享呼吸
在黄土地刷新成绩
我家大门常打开，开怀容纳天地
岁月绽放青春笑容，迎接这个日期
天大地大都是朋友请不用客气
画意诗情带笑意，只为等待你
北京欢迎你 像音乐感动你
让我们都加油去超越自己
北京欢迎你，有梦想谁都了不起
有勇气就会有奇迹
北京欢迎你，为你开天辟地
流动中的魅力充满着朝气
北京欢迎你，在太阳下分享呼吸
在黄土地刷新成绩
北京欢迎你，像音乐感动你
让我们都加油去超越自己
北京欢迎你，有梦想谁都了不起
有勇气就会有奇迹
我家大门常打开 开放怀抱等你
拥抱过就有了默契，你会爱上这里
不管远近都是客人请不用客气
相约好了在一起，我们欢迎你
北京欢迎你 为你开天辟地
流动中的魅力充满着朝气
北京欢迎你，在太阳下分享呼吸
在黄土地刷新成绩
我家大门常打开 开怀容纳天地
岁月绽放青春笑容 迎接这个日期
天大地大都是朋友请不用客气
画意诗情带笑意，只为等待你许茹芸
北京欢迎你，像音乐感动你
让我们都加油去超越自己游鸿明
北京欢迎你，有梦想谁都了不起
有勇气就会有奇迹金海心
北京欢迎你，为你开天辟地
流动中的魅力充满着朝气
北京欢迎你，在太阳下分享呼吸
在黄土地刷新成绩
北京欢迎你，像音乐感动你
让我们都加油去超越自己
北京欢迎你，有梦想谁都了不起
有勇气就会有奇迹付丽珊
北京欢迎你，有梦想谁都了不起
有勇气就会有奇迹
北京欢迎你 有梦想谁都了不起
有勇气就会有奇迹</description></item><item><title>Links for Blackberry</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/links-for-blackberry/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 04:56:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/links-for-blackberry/</guid><description>gmail : http://gmail.com/app
miniopera : http://mini.opera.com
Update System
0. prerequisites
1. rename/rm Vendor.xml in &amp;ldquo;program files&amp;rdquo;/&amp;ldquo;Common Files&amp;rdquo;/&amp;ldquo;Research In Motion&amp;rdquo;/AppLoader
2. loader.exe /nojvm will start the application installation.</description></item><item><title>Concert by Secret Garden</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/concert-by-secret-garden/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 22:36:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/concert-by-secret-garden/</guid><description>For me, they are awesome!
I know the Secret Garden almost ten years ago. I&amp;rsquo;m really being attractive by their music for long period.
And I couldn&amp;rsquo;t image I can ever get a chance to enjoy their music in live.
As Sherry said, even we are speaking in different language, but tonight we communicate with music.
Last Saturday, I spend several hours having a quick practice the Django, which is a web framework wrote in Python.</description></item><item><title>Back to Hangzhou</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/back-to-hangzhou/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 20:27:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/back-to-hangzhou/</guid><description>At this moment&amp;hellip;what can I recall about those two months&amp;hellip;
And we are leaving at 4 AM and arrive at Shanghai at 6pm.</description></item><item><title>Runnning Warcraft 3 in Widescreen</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/running-warcraft-3-in-widescreen/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 23:01:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/running-warcraft-3-in-widescreen/</guid><description>START &amp;gt; run &amp;gt; regedit
locate to:
HKEY_CURRENT_USER &amp;gt; Software &amp;gt; Blizzard Entertainment &amp;gt; Warcraft III &amp;gt; Video
Make below change in decimal format:
(Right click &amp;gt; Change &amp;gt; select &amp;ldquo;decimal&amp;rdquo; &amp;gt; fill in new value)
resheight = 1600
reswidth = 900
Replace width &amp;amp; height with whatever resolution you wanna play in, examples:
1280x720 16:9 Widescreen
1440x900 16:10 Widescreen
1680x1050 16:10 Widescreen
1920x1200 16:10 Widescreen
For Details</description></item><item><title>Hooters, Hangzhou</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/hooters-hangzhou/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2007 09:59:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/hooters-hangzhou/</guid><description>Michael asked for a party in the hooters since he&amp;rsquo;s going back to US a couple weeks later.
We really enjoyed ourselves I think, the beer, the chicken wings and of course hot girls.
Except the cost is expensive.
One guy here told that she&amp;rsquo;s preparing GRE and ToFEL. In another words she&amp;rsquo;s planning to study in US.
Sounds good. And it made me think that I had this plan before.</description></item><item><title>Exhausted and extremely happy</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/exhausted-and-extremely-happy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2007 20:36:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/exhausted-and-extremely-happy/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s great interesting to get a comment from a foreigner on previous Chinese post.
Maybe he&amp;rsquo;s interested in foreign language like Chinese, or something else.
And I have to say I&amp;rsquo;m not able to write every post in English just because of my little English skills.
I couldn&amp;rsquo;t express something in my mind exactly in English and mostly English is used for reporting something and instant communication.
On the Oct. 01 and Oct.</description></item><item><title>Boltech no more Boldtech</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/boltech-no-more-boldtech/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2007 19:44:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/boltech-no-more-boldtech/</guid><description>Ron announced a very important news this morning that Boldtech Systems has been acquired by Perficient, Inc. And GDC China became a part of the Perficient as well. According Ron&amp;rsquo;s words, we won&amp;rsquo;t get much change in short term in China but not including time&amp;amp;expense system and email system. More official information might come along next. A surprise definitely. Good news or bad news? who knows.
Detail news here.</description></item><item><title>Performance Testing?</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/performance-testing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2007 06:33:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/performance-testing/</guid><description>We are going to use JMeter to take the performance testing in our project.
Till now I have no idea about how to contribute it to the project.
I read several documentations at the official site, just finding I lost at the graph results and some concepts.
Also I failed to use the Assertion component to validate the response.
Have to continue researching.
These two days I back to write functional test using Selenium.</description></item><item><title>Resources in ongoing project</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/resources-in-ongoing-project/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2007 19:17:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/resources-in-ongoing-project/</guid><description>Hibernate 3.x
Spring Framework 2.x
DWR 1.x
Ext / Ext-Yui (javascript library)
JUnit 3.x
Cobertura 1.8 (coverage test)
Cruisecontrol (continuous integration toolkit)</description></item><item><title>New Office</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/new-office/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2007 23:28:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/new-office/</guid><description>We moved to a new office. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty nice and much better than the previous one.
The guys in back office did the great job!
But what&amp;rsquo;s the most disappointed thing was I still used a CRT monitor.
So I have to replace it with my own LCD monitor thus I will not have a network in home.
Probably it turn out to be a terrible thing.</description></item><item><title>Being a WOWer</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/being-wower/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2007 20:29:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/being-wower/</guid><description>I came back to the World of Warcraft after several months.
There was a new expansion the Burning crusade having lots of new features.
Two new races, new land named Outland,the highest level now is 70th,etc.
Those all seemed to be very interesting.
But after I launched the game and played for several levels, I found it&amp;rsquo;s almost the same as before.
Even new tasks,the process is identical. I mean in the lower level because I don&amp;rsquo;t what would happen after 60th level.</description></item><item><title>Researching week</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/researching-week/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2007 08:33:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/researching-week/</guid><description>Since we didn&amp;rsquo;t get the requirement for next release, so we spend the whole week to do some research about the technology we are using.
BIRT chart
I think design a simple chart in BIRT is very easy job. As we might introduce some charts for the project in the following release, I think preparing good SQL querys turns out to be more challege.
JBoss Portal
I learned how to configure portlet and portal page.</description></item><item><title>International Developer Conference (second day)</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/international-developer-conference/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2007 07:12:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/international-developer-conference/</guid><description>The first section this day is about SAAS. The guy spend lots of time introducing a platform designed by Alibaba.
And I didn&amp;rsquo;t find much interesting.
The second one is talking about the search engine and looking forward its future.
At third section, distinguished Engineer Mark Harpner from Sun Microsystems Inc. shared several products for implementing SOA.
Then Ben Wang from JBoss showed several JBoss open source project in SOA area.</description></item><item><title>China International Developer Conference</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/china-international-developer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2007 05:54:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/china-international-developer/</guid><description>首届中国网络工程师侠客行大会
This conference is arranged by Alibaba in Hang Zhou, China. Today is the first day.
In the morning, the first presentation was taken by Rasmus Lerdorf who is the father of PHP.
And the second guy is Jermy Zawodny,also a extreme famous from Yahoo Inc. and an expert in Yahoo search engine.
I couldn&amp;rsquo;t totally follow what they were talking without translation. But it&amp;rsquo;s fine.
Because I think that listening their talking was an interesting thing.</description></item><item><title>What have done these days</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/what-have-done-these-days/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2007 08:25:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/what-have-done-these-days/</guid><description>It seems that BIRT is a easy to learn and great reporting tool. I designed several reports with it.
Not very difficult and I also used its shared libraries feature, very cool. But we met a hard time of the drill through report, which also used shared libraries.
Everything goes well of each single report in BIRT Designer but failed when combining them through drill down,either deploying to Pentaho server.</description></item><item><title>Hope Genuine MS OS in lower price</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/hope-genuine-ms-os-in-lower-price/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2007 08:29:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/hope-genuine-ms-os-in-lower-price/</guid><description>I started to use Vista OS again and it indeed a fantastic Operation System I even experienced (And I also wish I will get Apple machine in future. ^^ ).
And it just has 30 days to use. What a pity! I do want to get a genuine copyright instead of cracking it.
But a genuine one is tooooo expensive for ordinary Chinese guys like me. I am sure most of us will still use a cracked Vista.</description></item><item><title>Get busy livin' or get busy dyin'</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/get-busy-livin-or-get-busy-dyin/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2007 08:02:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/get-busy-livin-or-get-busy-dyin/</guid><description>This was a quote from the film &amp;lt;The Shawshank Redemption&amp;gt;, which made me think a lot.
Its main theme is hope. And recently I also think about it. Because I wonder almost everything should be possible and you should not lose faith.
It&amp;rsquo;s much worth to take two hours in watching this film and also for more than once.
This time I took a good rest and feel peaceful.
上星期参加林健的婚礼，顺便在逛了下苏州。城市很有特色，蛮值得一去。</description></item><item><title>Http Header Referer</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/http-header-referer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2007 05:20:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/http-header-referer/</guid><description>It seems that Pentaho Pre-Configged server doesn&amp;rsquo;t support reporting security.That means everyone can see the report if he know the URL.
And I found out I could get the users' role set in JBoss portal session but not Pentaho session since I used two filter in both session.
Then I think they are different sessions and I tried to find the relationship but failed.
So I didnot know how to transfer the role infor from JBoss portal session to Pentaho session.</description></item><item><title>Two interations</title><link>https://freizl.github.io/posts/two-interations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 06:53:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://freizl.github.io/posts/two-interations/</guid><description>Well,the iteration 2 was done when COB this Friday.
Iteration 1 last week just setted the environment of developing and testing.
Got the tools: MySQL Database,a open ETL tool named CloverETL, Pentaho BI platform, xPlanner,Bugzilla.
We just used a litter part of Pentaho,such as reporting (basic on JFreeChart) and portal (basic on JBoss portal).
This week, we have got the Authentication task completed, which using JBoss LDAP login module against MS AD.</description></item></channel></rss>